Karthikayini P

FULL STACK DEVELOPER.

Phone +91 8940151398

E-Mail karthikayinipalanivel@gmail.com

Address Coimbatore,India.

LinkedIn karthikayini P

 Software development professional with experience in developing and designing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular, Node.js, and React. Adept at developing and deploying complex backend systems, web services and databases.

- Skillful creating servers and databases for functionality and designing and developing APIs. Hardworking collaborator with track record of superior results.
- Tech-savvy Full Stack web Developer proficient in fundamental front-end languages and server-side languages. In-depth knowledge of MySQL and MongoDB.

SKILLS

- HTML expertise
- CSS proficiency
- Java Full Stack
- Stack Development
- Website optimization
- JavaScript programming
- React
- Advanced SAP knowledge
- Front End Web Development

EDUCATION

M.A.M College of Engineering-Trichy,India. Electrical And Electronic Engineering

2018-2022

Final grade [85]%.

WORK HISTORY

DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Social Commerce Buisness Januar2021-January2022

- Developed and executed multiple print and digital marketing efforts to enhance brand visibility.
- Mentored local personnel on best practices and protocols to maximize productivity.
- Oversaw preparation of marketing copy, images, videos, emails, and other collateral.
- Improved website visibility through development and implementation of SEO strategies.
- Continually maintained and improved company's reputation and positive image in markets served.

ACADEMIC COUNSELOR

Raptor Technologies Coimbatore,India July2022-April2023

- Provided support and guidance to students experiencing academic and personal troubles.
- Provided support and guidance to students experiencing academic and personal troubles.
- Determined validity and reliability of data gathering methods. Assessed data gathering methods for validity and eliability purporses.
- Consulted with candidates on primary research, data collection, bibliographies and model writing assistance.

Design and Implementation of Electric Spring grid Tied System.

The objective of the Prject design of Electric Spring for Compensation of voltage and current for improved Power Factor for Power Quality improvement.

٨	Ē	П	۱Λ	T	\cap	N	C
-	٩r	ш	IH	ш		ı١٧	

Experience Letter.

Full stack development(Course completed certificate).

AutoCAD Electrical Certificate.

Hindi Certificate.

SOFTWARE

AutoCAD

E-CAD

CERTIFICATIONS

[TCIL-IT] License - [31-12-2021]

AutoCAD Electrical.

[Dakshina Bharat Hini Prachar Sabha MADRAS] Training - [06-10-2016]

Hindi Certificate.

[IPCS] Training - [18.08.2019]

Workshop of Electrical and Electronic Engg.